A Guide to the Edward H. Peeples, Jr. Papers, n.d., 1915, 1920s-2005
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Miscellaneous audio and visual materials (slides, audio and video recordings, phonographs, photographs), publications, ephemera, and oversize materials. 1930s-2004 (Box 22-36)
  - Photographs - Poverty in Richmond, June 1966 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - Poverty in Nottoway Co., Rt. 307, May 2002 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Photographs - President Clinton signs in Richmond, ca. 1998/1999 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Photographs - Rockett's Landing, late 19th century postcard n.d. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Photographs - Rockett's Landing Area, July 2002 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - Scenes, Deer on Skyline Drive, 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - Scenes in Richmond, April 1980 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Photographs - State Prison, New Jersey, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Photographs - Street person, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Photographs - Street people, Fan District, Richmond, 2002 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - Street people, Strawberry Street, Richmond, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Photographs - Sue from Spring show at Anderson Gallery (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Photographs - Telemarketing sweat shop, Richmond, April 1990 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Photographs - Trip to Harrisonburg, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Photographs - Virginia scenes from Heartfields, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Photographs - Virginia Historical Society Civil Rights Exhibit, 2004 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Photographs - Main Street Grill (Wally Bless), Richmond, Virginia, June 1987 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Photographs - Pictures, 1-100 II n.d. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - Pictures, negatives 1-100 II n.d. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - Pictures 1-100, 101-149, 1960s (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - Pictures, negatives 1-100, 101-149, 1960s (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - 2000-1 Ancarrow's Landing, Slave Docks ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - 2000-2 Ancarrow's Landing ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - 2000-3 Briar's Slave Trail ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - 2000-4 Briar's Slave Trail ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - 2000-5 Canal Boat, Jewish cemetery ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - 2000-6 Gabriel's Revolt sites ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - 2000-7 Henrico Co. Courthouse in Richmond, site of first City Hall ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Photographs - 2000-8 Museum of the Confederacy ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Photographs - 2000-9 railroad tracks and Richmond City skyline ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Photographs - 2000-10 Slave Market sites ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - 2000-11 Slave trade sites ca. 2000 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Camera used by Peeples when taking photographs in the 1960s including the photographs of schools in Prince Edward County, ca. early 1960s camera (Box 36, Folder 1)